So once again we're going to replace the one
remaining part of our test, that still has a
standard database. Let's actually get rid of our database.
That leaves us with this lonely insert statement. Once
again, like with everything else, we're going to replace that
with a content resolver call. And of course we're
actually not going to be inserting the table. We're going
inserting the content URI. Getting rid of the nulls.
Of course this doesn't return a location row ID.
That's alright. We can pull it from the URI. Using
the helper function from content URI's, we can leave
that insert in there, although it's not necessary. And the
rest of everything should pretty much be as it
always is. We're no longer using a database at all
within test provider, but entirely using the content provider.
Let's run our tests and see if they still work.
[BLANK_AUDIO]
And they all pass. Congratulations, we now
have a fully functioning content provider that can
both insert and query. But, of course,
there are other things you might want to do
with the content provider. Now, we're not
actually going to use any of these things
in Sunshine. But it's really important to know.
So, I suggest you actually implement these functions.